fastticket.in 2015-06-10

# Fastticket Privacy Policy | fastticket.in

**FASTTICKET** is committed to protect your privacy and as part of our policy we do our utmost to protect the personal information of users of our services. Through this policy we intend to explain how we treat personal information that our users share with us.

The personal information collected by us can include details such as your name, address, telephone number, etc. We assure our users that we adhere to strict standards that are in place for protecting user data privacy with context to usage of our web site.

##### How We Treat USER Information

Visitors of **FASTTICKET** website can use its services anonymously, i.e. without revealing any type of personal information. We keep a track of the URL of domains through which you visit our site. This is done for the purpose of analyzing the data for trends and statistics and the process does not reveal personal information of the user in any way.

We may, from time to time, need to collect personal information from you that can consist of small details such as your name, address or mobile or landline number. We intend to notify you prior to collecting such information and also give information about how we intend to treat the information.

It is totally at your discretion whether you do or do not want to provide us with the required information. In case you choose not to give us the requested information, you will still be able to browse the **FASTTICKET** website, but in a limited way as you may be not be able to access some of the options, offers or services.

We provide users of our services with login id and password to logon and avail our services in secure mode. With user’s acceptance of Terms and Conditions of Service agreement, FASTTICKET holds no responsibility for keeping user password confidential and also for any and all activities that arise from abuse or misuse of the password. Users are advised to change their passwords periodically to keep them confidential.

We may use your personal information for various purposes such as to verify user identity as and when required, to provide the services requested by you, to help you subscribe to FASTTICKET, to administer and manage services including, charging, billing and collecting debts.

We may also need user information to suggest users about improvements that could be made to our services, or to gain an understanding about the information and communication needs of our users so that **FASTTICKET** can provide better services. The user information can also be used for performing appropriate checks for user’s credit-worthiness.

**FASTTICKET** would like to assure its users that it stores, keeps or accesses user information only for the purpose of providing services to its users and not for any other purpose whatsoever.

##### FASTTICKET And Cookies

Pages on our website may use cookies that help us serve you better with customized information when you revisit our site. Cookies are small-sized text files which are stored on your computer hard drive.

Information collected via cookies is analyzed by us to make improvements to our services. You can make necessary settings to your browser to receive notifications when you receive cookies. This allows you to make a choice to either accept or deny cookies.

##### Sharing Your Information

**FASTTICKET** will not sell, trade or disclose to third parties any information derived from the registration for, or use of, any online service (including names and addresses) without the consent of the user or customer (except as required by or other legal process or in the case of imminent physical harm to the user or others).

**FASTTICKET** makes every attempt to protect the information you share with us. We have implemented technology and security features and strict policy guidelines to safeguard the privacy of your personally identifiable information from unauthorized access and improper use or disclosure. FASTTICKET will continue to enhance its security procedures as new technology becomes available.

##### Changes To Our Privacy Policy

FASTTICKET reserves full rights to make required modifications to its Privacy Policy as and when it deems necessary. If we make changes to our privacy policy, we will post the revised policy on this page and you will be able to view the revised date at the bottom of this page. You are also requested to read this page at regular intervals to keep updated about our current private policies.

**FASTTICKET** attempts to keep user information private and to guard user privacy by continuously enforcing its privacy policies. The user can contact us in case you have any questions regarding our services and we will do our best to resolve your inquiry as soon as possible.
